# **Jordan Stotts**

Cell: (515) 401-2874 jordanstotts22@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/jordanstotts

I am a software engineer with skills in front-end and back-end web development. My previous career as a professional basketball player overseas has given me insight into what I want my career after playing to look like: building and maintaining sports betting/sports centered websites that have a great user experience. In this next phase of my career, I seek a role as a web developer at a company where I can work on solving problems that help make websites function more efficiently for everyone involved as well as learn, grow, and continue to master my craft.

#### SKILLS:

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- React

#### PROJECTS:

Git hub link here

#### WORK EXPERIENCE:

Production Coordinator, September 2020 – December 2021

InterContinental Capital Group, West Des Moines, IA

- Helped manage pipeline of 15-20 FHA, VA, and USDA loans per month
- Assisted with inputting borrower information, communicate with clients as necessary, as well as ordering third party documentation
- Worked with management to provide support in various stages of the lending process for loan officers and processors

#### Professional Basketball Player, December 2016 – May 2020

Ocklebo Basketball Club, Starlites Basketball Club, Moncton Miracles, Europe and Canada

- Played professional basketball at the highest level in Sweden, Malta, and Canada
- Trained every day in season with the teams as well as on my own during each off season
- Attended team appearances that included coaching

# Event Staff, October 2013 – May 2016

Sioux Falls Pentagon, Sioux Falls, South Dakota

- Performed tasks such as ushering, ticketing, program distribution, and general customer service
- Assisted with youth basketball and volleyball tournaments on weekends

• Helped set up for all major events held (G-League basketball, MMA fights, music concerts, etc.)

## **EDUCATION:**

Software Engineering Immersive Bootcamp, General Assembly Remote, December 2021 - March 2022

Bachelor of Arts
Sports Management Degree with a Minor in Entrepreneurial Studies
University of Sioux Falls, Sioux Falls, South Dakota
Cumulative GPA 3.3

## **ACTIVITIES/AWARDS:**

University of Sioux Falls

Division II Collegiate Basketball:	2012 - 2016
Athletic (basketball) scholarship recipient	2013- 2016
Provost (academic) scholarship recipient	2012 - 2016